Guide to the Mick Moloney Irish-American Music and Popular Culture Papers AIA.031.003
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Academic, 1889-2011; 3 boxes
  - University of Pennsylvania: General, 1988-1992 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Villanova University: Exams, undated (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Villanova University: General (Folder 1), 1981-1982 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Villanova University: General (Folder 2), 1989-1992 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Villanova University: Notes on Class Readings, undated (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Villanova University: Syllabi and Bibliographies, 1977-1990 (Box 22, Folder 43)
- Series IV: Song and Music Collecting, 1867-2000; 2 boxes
  Series IV: Song and Music Collecting, 1867-2000 contains lyrics, tunes, and songs in published and manuscript form collected by Dr. Moloney for research, personal, and performance use. Of particular note are John Ward's Private Collection of Irish Comic Songs, twenty photocopied songsters, and manuscripts of dance tunes, some of which are Moloney's compositions.
  - Articles: Songs, undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Articles: Songwriting, 1916 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Broadsides, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Broadsides: Cork Songmakers Club, undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Choral Music: Louisville Chorus, undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Comics: Book of Ballads and Sagas, 1995-1996 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Dance Books: "Good Morning" Music, Calls, and Directions for Old-Time Dancing, 1943 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Dance Books: Untitled- Excerpt, undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Lyrics: Collections, undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Lyrics: Manuscripts (Folder 1), undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Lyrics: Manuscripts (Folder 2), undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Reciter: Erin's Own Reciter, undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Reciter: Irish Dialect Poems and Recitations, 1899 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Songbooks: 51 Lucky Irish Classics, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Songbooks: Best Music Hall and Variety Songs (excerpts), 1972 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Songbooks: Flashes of Merriment: A Century of Humorous Songs in America, 1805-1905, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Songbooks: Folksongs and Ballads Popular in Ireland, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Songbooks: Foster Songs, 1942 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Songbooks: Hansen's Irish Songbook, undated (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Songbooks: Irish Folksinger's Album, circa 1957 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Songbooks: Irish Ireland Songbook, undated (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Songbooks: Irish Tavern Folio of Humor Songs, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Songbooks: Irish Woman's Songbook, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Songbooks: Penny Buns and Roses, undated (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Songbooks: Rubank Holiday Collection, 1932 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Songbooks: Sing Song Sing-a-Long, undated (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Songbooks: Tommy Sands Songbook, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Songbooks: New Song Fest, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Songbooks: Songs of Kiwanis, 1927 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Songbooks: Treasure Chest of Irish Songs Jigs and Reels, 1943 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Songbooks: Untitled, undated (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Songbooks: John Ward's Collection of Irish Comic Songs, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Songbooks: John Ward's Private Collection of Irish Comic Songs, 1943 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Song Catalogs: Irish Industries Depot, Inc., undated (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Song Collecting: Correspondence, 1977-2000 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Song Collecting: General, undated (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Song Collectors: Tom Heddeman, circa 1900 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Song Collectors: Dee Hicks, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Song Collectors: "O'Donnell's Collection", 1976 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Song Ideas, undated (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Song Index: Peter Cassidy, undated (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Song Index: Peter Kennedy, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Songs: Civil War (Folder 1), undated (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Songs: Civil War (Folder 2), undated (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Songs: Declan Forde, undated (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Songs: General: A-C, undated (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Songs: General: D-F, undated (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Songs: General: G-J, undated (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Songs: General: L-N, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Songs: General: 0-S, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Songs: General: T-Y, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Songs: Liner Notes- Archie Fisher, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Songs: Liner Notes- Ireland: The Final Struggle, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Songs: Liner Notes- Bill Staines, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Songs: Ohio Canals, 1952-1992 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Songs: Joe Reary, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Songs: Scores- Manuscripts, undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Songs to Learn, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Songsters: A Bit O' Blarney, 1903 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Songsters: Early Ballads in Ireland: 1968-1985 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Songsters: Favorite Old Irish Songs, undated (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Songsters: Irish Songs and Ballads, undated (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Songsters: My Father Soul'd Charcoal Songster, 1870 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Songsters: New City Songsters, 1969-1971 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Songsters: Old-Time Song and Ballads of Ireland, 1901 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Songsters: Harry Osborne and Fanny Wentworth's Irish Comedian, 1878 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Songsters: Paddy's the Boy Songster, 1867 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Songsters: Johnny Patterson's Great Inter-Ocean Circus Songster, undated (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Songsters: Johnny Patterson's Great London Circus Singers, undated (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Songsters: Prize Song Book, 1893 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Songsters: Pat Reilly's McGrogan the Cop, undated (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Songsters: St. Patrick's Day Songster, undated (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Songsters: Songs of Glen na Mona, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Songsters: Universal Irish Song Book (Folder 1), 1890 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Songsters: Universal Irish Song Book (Folder 2), 1890 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Songsters: Universal Irish Song Book (Folder 3), 1890 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Songsters: Untitled, undated (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Songsters: Wehman Brothers' Pocket-Sized Irish Song Book No. 1, 1909 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Songsters: Various- Excerpts, undated (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Tunebooks: Harding's Collection of 100 Jigs and Reels, 1896 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Tunebooks: Treasure Chest of Dances Old and New, 1937 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Tunes: Manuscripts, undated (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Tunes: Manuscripts- Tommy Caulfield, undated (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Tunes: Manuscripts- Selected and Arranged by Eugene O'Donnell, undated (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Tunes: Moloney Compositions, undated (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Tunes: Printed Scores, undated (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Tunes: Sheet Music, undated (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Voice of the People: Songs and History of Ireland (excerpts), 1982 (Box 24, Folder 40)
- Series V: Concert Memorabilia, 1971-2011; 2 boxes
  Series V: Concert Memorabilia, 1971-2011 consists of programs, flyers, brochures, and ephemera accumulated during Dr. Moloney's performance career. Of particular note are many oversized items, including early Johnstons posters and a Spanish-language poster promoting the 1985 Festival of Mountain Music and Dance Central American tour.
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Posters, 1978-1988 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera (Folder 1), 1982 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera (Folder 2), 1982 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Posters, May, 1985 (Flat-file-folder 6)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera (Folder 1), 1986 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera (Folder 2), 1986 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera (Folder 1), 1987 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera (Folder 2), 1987 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera (Folder 3), 1987 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera (Folder 1), 1988 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera (Folder 2), 1988 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Posters, 1990-1995 (Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera (Folder 1), 1993 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera (Folder 2), 1993 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera (Folder 3), 1993 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera (Folder 1), 1994 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera (Folder 2), 1994 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera (Folder 3), 1994 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera (Folder 1), 1995 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera (Folder 2), 1995 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera (Folder 1), 1996 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera (Folder 2), 1996 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera (Folder 1), 1997 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera (Folder 2), 1997 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Posters, 2001-2004 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera, 2001-2005 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera, 2007-2011 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera (Folder 1), undated (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera (Folder 2), undated (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera (Folder 3), undated (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera (Folder 4), undated (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera (Folder 5), undated (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Programs, Fliers, Brochures and Ephemera (Folder 6), undated (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Posters, undated (Box 37, Folder 4, Box 38)
  - Posters (Flat-file-folder 16 Right)
- Series VI: Photographs, circa 1930-2002; 8 boxes
  Series VI: Photographs, circa 1930-2002 consists of slides, prints, and negatives of performers, events, and venues that appear in both the Papers and Field Recordings subcollections. Subjects with extensive coverage include Dr. Moloney's performing partnerships with Eugene O'Donnell, Robbie O'Connell, and Jimmy Keane; Moloney's package tours of Ireland and Scotland; the 1987 International Village Fair hosted by Philadelphia's International House; step dancing classes and competitions (some featuring Jean and Cara Butler); and slides prepared for Dr. Moloney's lectures. Of particular note are contact sheets documenting informal gathering of musicians and a 35 mm print of Did Your Mother Come From Ireland?, Dr. Moloney's 1981film on the Mulvihill School of Irish Music in the Bronx.
  - Subseries A: Slides, 2011
    - Augusta Heritage Center, August 1994 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Augusta Heritage Center, undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Blended Scotch, undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Cahill, Eddie, January 1978 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Cahill, Eddie, March 1978 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Carroll, Liz, May 1983 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Celebration of Afro-American Folklife (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), June 1982 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Cleveland Musicians, undated (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Coen, Jack and Fr. Charlie, April 1977 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Comhaltas Convention, undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Dance: Classes Featuring Jean and Cara Butler (Folder 1), undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Dance: Classes Featuring Jean and Cara Butler (Folder 2), undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Dance: Classes Featuring Jean and Cara Butler (Folder 3), undated (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Dance: Classes (Folder 1), undated (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Dance: Classes (Folder 2), undated (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Dance: Competitions (Folder 1), July 1994 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Dance: Competitions (Folder 2), July 1994 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Dance: Competitions (Folder 3), July 1994 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Dance: Competitions (Folder 4), July 1994 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Dance: Competitions (Folder 5), July 1994 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Dance: Competitions (Folder 6), July 1994 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Dance: Competitions (Folder 7), July 1994 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Dance: Competitions (Folder 8), July 1994 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Dance: Competitions (Folder 9), August 1995 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Dance: Competitions (Folder 10), undated (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Dance: Competitions (Folder 11), undated (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Dance: Competitions (Folder 12), undated (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Dance: Competitions (Folder 13), undated (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Dance: Competitions (Folder 14), undated (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Dance: Competitions (Folder 15), undated (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Dance: Competitions (Folder 16), undated (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Dance: Competitions (Folder 17), undated (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Dervish, undated (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Egan Family, undated (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance (Folder 1), 1985 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance (Folder 2), 1985 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance (Folder 3), 1985 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance (Folder 4), 1985 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance (Folder 5), 1985 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance (Folder 6), 1985 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance (Folder 7), 1985 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Festivals, September 1986 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Festivals, undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Festivals: Mount St. Vincent's, Bronx, NY (Folder 1), June 1994 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Festivals: Mount St. Vincent's, Bronx, NY (Folder 2), June 1994 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Festivals: Washington, D.C., July 1994 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Festival of Traditional American Dance, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Fitzpatrick, John and Maureen, June 1978 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Flanagan, Mike, October 1977 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Glen Echo Festival, July 1980 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - International House: Seventy-Fifth Anniversary, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - International House: Children's Folk Services, January 1982 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - International House: Community Events and Apprenticeships (Folder 1), 1984 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - International House: Community Events and Apprenticeships (Folder 2), 1987 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - International House: Community Events and Apprenticeships (Folder 3), 1988 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - International House: Community Events and Apprenticeships (Folder 4), 1989 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - International House: Community Events and Apprenticeships (Folder 5), 1990 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - International House: Jewish Festival, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - International House: Programming- Balkan, February 1978 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - International House: Programming- Caribbean (Folder 1), May 1978 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - International House: Programming- Caribbean (Folder 2), May 1978 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - International House: Programming- General, 1978-1982 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - International House: Programming- Irish and Ukrainian, November 1977 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - International House: Programming- Italian (Folder 1), April 1978 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - International House: Programming- Italian (Folder 2), April 1978 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - International House: Programming- Junior Gala, March 1978 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - International House: Programming- Jewish (Folder 1), April 1978 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - International House: Programming- Jewish (Folder 2), April 1978 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - International House: Programming- Mummies and Clowns (Folder 1), May 1978 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - International House: Programming- Mummies and Clowns (Folder 2), March 1978 (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - International House: Programming- Polish (Folder 1), May 1978 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - International House: Programming- Polish (Folder 2), May 1978 (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - International House: Programming- Polish (Folder 3), May 1978 (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - International House: Programming- Polish (Folder 4), May 1978 (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - International House: Programming- Polish (Folder 5), May 1978 (Box 28, Folder 40)
    - International House: Programming- Turkish, April 1978 (Box 28, Folder 41)
    - International House: Programming- Unidentified, February 1978 (Box 28, Folder 42)
    - International Village Fair: General, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 43)
    - International Village Fair: Color Slides AA-AE, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 44)
    - International Village Fair: Color Slides AF-AK, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 45)
    - International Village Fair: Color Slides AL-AP, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 46)
    - International Village Fair: Color Slides AR-AW, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 47)
    - International Village Fair: Color Slides AX-BB, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 48)
    - International Village Fair: Color Slides BC-BG, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - International Village Fair: Color Slides BH-BL, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - International Village Fair: Color Slides BM-BR, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - International Village Fair: Color Slides BS-BX, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - International Village Fair: Color Slides- Unlabeled, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - International Village Fair: Color Slides Log, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Irish Festivals: Vendors (Folder 1), undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Irish Festivals: Vendors (Folder 2), undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Irish Music Academy of Cleveland, January 1995 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Lecture Slides: Book of Kells, Celtic Art, undated (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Lecture Slides: Irish-American Music on the Stage (Folder 1), undated (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Lecture Slides: Irish-American Music on the Stage (Folder 2), undated (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Lecture Slides: Irish-American Music on the Stage (Folder 3), undated (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Lecture Slides: Irish-American Music on the Stage (Folder 4), undated (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Lecture Slides: Irish-American Music on the Stage (Folder 5), undated (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - McNultys, undated (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Milwaukee Irish Fest (Folder 1), undated (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Milwaukee Irish Fest (Folder 2), undated (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Milwaukee Irish Fest (Folder 3), undated (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Moloney, Mick, undated (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Moloney, Mick: Home Studio, June 1978 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Moloney, Mick: Wedding, May 1976 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Moloney, Mick, Winifred Horan and Tommy Sands, undated (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Moloney, Mick, Robbie O'Connell and Jimmy Keane, February 1984 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Moloney, Mick, Robbie O'Connell, Jimmy Keane and Eileen Ivers, September 1986 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Moloney, Mick and Eugene O'Donnell (Folder 1), 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Moloney, Mick and Eugene O'Donnell (Folder 2), 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Moloney, Mick and Eugene O'Donnell (Folder 3), undated (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Mulvihill, Martin and Family, June 1981 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Montserrat (Folder 1), August 1994 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Montserrat (Folder 2), undated (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - NEA: Knoxville Documentation Project- Color Slides (Folder 1), circa 1980 (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - NEA: Knoxville Documentation Project- Color Slides (Folder 2), circa 1980 (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - Neary, Eleanor Kane, May 1980 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - Package Tours: Ireland (Folder 1), October 1993 (Box 29, Folder 35)
    - Package Tours: Ireland (Folder 2), July 1994 (Box 29, Folder 36)
    - Package Tours: Ireland (Folder 3), July 1994 (Box 29, Folder 37)
    - Package Tours: Ireland (Folder 4), August 1994 (Box 29, Folder 38)
    - Package Tours: Ireland (Folder 5), August 1994 (Box 29, Folder 39)
    - Package Tours: Ireland (Folder 6), August 1995 (Box 29, Folder 40)
    - Package Tours: Ireland (Folder 7), September 1995 (Box 29, Folder 41)
    - Package Tours: Ireland (Folder 8), undated (Box 29, Folder 42)
    - Package Tours: Ireland (Folder 9), undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Package Tours: Ireland (Folder 10), undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Package Tours: Ireland (Folder 11), undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Package Tours: Ireland (Folder 12), undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Package Tours: Ireland (Folder 13), undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Package Tours: Ireland (Folder 14), undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Package Tours: Ireland (Folder 15), undated (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Package Tours: Ireland (Folder 16), undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Package Tours: Ireland (Folder 17), undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Package Tours: Ireland (Folder 18), undated (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Package Tours: Ireland (Folder 19), undated (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Package Tours: Ireland- Commercial Slides, undated (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Package Tours: Ireland- Selected (Folder 1), undated (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Package Tours: Ireland- Selected (Folder 2), undated (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Package Tours: Ireland- Selected (Folder 3), undated (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Package Tours: Northern Ireland and Scotland (Folder 1), undated (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Package Tours: Northern Ireland and Scotland (Folder 2), undated (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Package Tours: Northern Ireland and Scotland (Folder 3), undated (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Package Tours: Scotland, undated (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Package Tours: Tory Island, undated (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Philadelphia Ceili Group Festival, undated (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Reavy, Ed, January 1978 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Robinson, LaVaughan, undated (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - St. Malachy's, undated (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Sessions (Folder 1), 1976-1981 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Sessions (Folder 2), undated (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Shannon, Joe, May 1983 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Teahan, Terry "Cuz", April 1977 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Unidentified (Folder 1), June 1981 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Unidentified (Folder 2), undated (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - White House Performance, undated (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - World's Fair of 1982 (Knoxville, Tennessee), August 1982 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - World's Fair of 1982 (Knoxville, Tennessee): Slideshow- People Around Here (Folder 1) (Box 30, Folder 33)